cybertechhelp.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy : Cyber Tech Help

Please note: if you have any questions about the Cyber Tech Help™ Privacy Policy please contact us.

Cyber Tech Help has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Cyber Tech Help.

## IP and Cookies 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. (We use cookies to store visitors preferences).

## Ad Servers 

With respect to Ad Servers: Cyber Tech Help partners with Google to provide content relevent image and text-based adverts only.

## Registration 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

## Links 

This site contains links to other sites. Cyber Tech Help is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security 

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

## Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can use our contact form to contact us directly regarding this issue.

## Contacting the Website 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, your dealings with this Web site, or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us using our contact form.
